<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MeriSafety</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer">NavigationDrawerActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="facebook_app_id">429196797477314</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb429196797477314</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="aboutapp">MeriSafety app provides that needed safety to everyone who downloads it.  All you have to do is create an account on this app and register a guardian\'s contact details and email details.\n\nWhenever you are in an emergency, be it medical, transportation, harassment you can press on the required button.\n\nMeriSafety app will automatically call your registered guardian and also E-mail and message them your current location.\n\nThis app will help you by showing you the nearby hospitals, bus stops, police stations.  Once you feel you are out of danger, you can also de-activate your alert. The message for the sane will be delivered to your registered guardian.</string>
    <string name="about_abhi">He worked on the documentation of the whole Application, etc.</string>
    <string name="about_paras">Team Leader and worked efficient to control, manage, test, debug, and finalize the whole app, etc.</string>
    <string name="about_priya">She worked fluently on the UI, functionality, and maps of the app, etc.</string>
    <string name="about_ridhi">She worked on the Core UI of the App including login, signup, team, about in the app, etc.</string>
    <string name="about_sid">He worked on the complete Database Connectivity and program flow of the app, etc.</string>
    <string name="about_sunny">He worked on the Maps, Permissions and the contact retrieval in the app, etc.</string>
    <string name="self_defence">The condition of being protected from or unlikely to cause danger, risk, or injury is safety.\n\nThe defence of one\'s person or interests, especially through the use of physical force, which is permitted in certain cases as an answer to a charge of violent crime.\n\nFive Self-Defenence moves you must know.\n\n1. Open Hand Strike.\n\n2. Kick to the groin.\n\n3. 360 or outside defence.\n\n4. Handbag grab or any aggressive grab.\n\n5. Attack from the ground.</string>
</resources>
